

SLIL PUANGPOOM

Software Engineer

THANK YOU FOR VISITING

https://blink-me-code-next.vercel.app

ABOUT ME

I have 5 years experienced in software development. I am a fullstack developer with modern technology stack like React.js / Next.js / Golang. You can see more about my information in my own website.



slil.puangpoom@gmail.com



087-500-6783



Bangkok, Bangsue, 10800

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Industrial Engineering Chulalongkorn University

2013-05 / 2017-07

EXPERIENCE

Dime! by Kiatnakin Phatra 2023-10 / Present Software Engineer

- Implement backend services with Golang
- Microservice, Redis, RabbitMQ
- Mobile development with flutter

Ascend Group (Ascend Bit) 2022-07 / 2023-10 Senior Software Engineer

- Blockchain projects (wallet /point / loyalty program)
- Next.js / React / Redux / Design system storybook
- Web3, DApp

Refinitiv An LESG Business 2021-07 / 2022-06 Software Engineer

- Data platform project
- React / Redux / Jest
- Working with international teams
- Agile software development

Hatari wireless Software Engineer

2018-10 / 2021-06

- Software house with variety type of projects
- Work as Fullstack developer with startup culture
- React / C# .Net Core / AWS

EXPERTISE

- React / Next.js
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- MUI / Tailwind / Bootstrap
- Redux / Jest / Web3
- Golang / Gin
- Node.js /Nest.js
- MongoDB / MySQL / PostgreSQL